let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Get Rich or Die Tryin' by 50 Cent went platinum how many times?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "2",
      "3",
      "8",
      "5"
    ]
  }, 
    { 
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who said this: 'I'm that cat by the bar toasting to the good life.'",
    answer: "50 Cent",
    options: [
      "50 Cent",
      "Dr. Dre",
      "Jermaine Dupri",
      "Eminem"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The album, It's Dark and Hell Is Hot , was released by which hip hop group or artist?",
    answer: "DMX",
    options: [
      "Juvenile",
      "Run–D.M.C.",
      "Salt-n-Pepa",
      "DMX"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "From which song did Coolio get the beat for his song 'Gangsta's Paradise'?",
    answer: "Pastime Paradise",
    options: [
      "Old Time Paradise",
      "Part-time Paradise",
      "Pastime Paradise",
      "Love's Paradise"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Lauryn Hill was a member of which band formed in 1994?",
    answer: "The Fugees",
    options: [
      "The Pogues",
      "The Fugees",
      "All Saints",
      "Salt - N - Pepa"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Whose debut album is 'Illmatic'?",
    answer: "Nas",
    options: [
      "EPMD",
      "Ol' Dirty Bastard",
      "Nas",
      "Afu-Ra"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who was the first artist to remix Drake's song 'Started from the Bottom'?",
    answer: "Wiz Khalifa",
    options: [
      "Juicy J",
      "Tyga",
      "Snoop Dogg",
      "Wiz Khalifa"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The album, 'Graduation' was released by which artist?",
    answer: "Kanye West",
    options: [
      "Will Smith",
      "Nelly",
      "Kanye West",
      "Dr. Dre"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What was the name of The Game's debut album in 2005?",
    answer: "The Documentary",
    options: [
      "The TV Show",
      "The Game",
      "The Documentary",
      "The Movie"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Whose debut album was called 'Reasonable Doubt'?",
    answer: "Jay-Z",
    options: [
      "Jay-Z",
      "Notorious B.I.G",
      "P.Diddy",
      "2pac"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Complete the name of this famous rap artist. 'Chris _____'",
    answer: "Brown",
    options: [
      "Breezy",
      "White",
      "Brown",
      "Black"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The album, The College Dropout , was released by which hip hop artist?",
    answer: "Kanye West",
    options: [
      "Eminem",
      "Kanye West",
      "Jay-Z",
      "Ludacris"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Whose album is 'The Chronic'?",
    answer: "Dr. Dre",
    options: [
      "Ice Cube",
      "Eazy E",
      "MC Ren",
      "Dr. Dre"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Who is one of hip hop's most successful producers?",
    answer: "Dr. Dre",
    options: [
      "Dr. Pepper",
      "Sir. Dre",
      "Dr. Dre",
      "Mr. Dre"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The best selling album, The Eminem Show, released by Eminem was released In what year?",
    answer: "2002",
    options: [
      "2003",
      "1990",
      "2000",
      "2002"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Dwayne Michael Carter is better known as what to his fans?",
    answer: "Lil Wayne",
    options: [
      "50 Cent",
      "Lil Wayne",
      "Rick Ross",
      "Drake"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Tupac was killed in a drive by shooting in which US city in 1996?",
    answer: "Las Vegas",
    options: [
      "Detroit",
      "Los Angeles",
      "Las Vegas",
      "New York"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The album, Raising Hell , was released by which hip hop group or artist?",
    answer: "Run–D.M.C.",
    options: [
      "Salt-n-Pepa",
      "Makaveli",
      "Run–D.M.C.",
      "DMX"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Who are the '03 Bonnie And Clyde'?",
    answer: "Jay-Z and Beyonce",
    options: [
      "Eminem and Kim",
      "50 Cent and Olivia",
      "Lil John and Mary J Blige",
      "Jay-Z and Beyonce"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The album, 'Vol. 3... Life and Times of S. Carter', was released by which artist?",
    answer: "Jay-Z",
    options: [
      "Lil Wayne",
      "Jay-Z",
      "Drake",
      "Kanye West"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "The album, 'Ghetto D', was released by which artist?",
    answer: "Master P",
    options: [
      "Silkk the Shocker",
      "Mystikal",
      "Lil Romeo",
      "Master P"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Eminem starred in the film '8 Mile', set in his real life home town, which is what city?",
    answer: "Detroit",
    options: [
      "Detroit",
      "Chicago",
      "Denver",
      "Minneapolis"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "The best selling album, All Eyez On Me, released by 2Pac was released In what year?",
    answer: "1996",
    options: [
      "1986",
      "1997",
      "1996",
      "1998"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "The album, The Black Album , was released by which hip hop group or artist?",
    answer: "Jay-Z",
    options: [
      "Lil Wayne",
      "Jay-Z",
      "Eminem",
      "Ludacris"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "In 1994 Biggie Smalls married which R&B artist?",
    answer: "Faith Evans",
    options: [
      "Faith Hill",
      "Missy Elliott",
      "Lauren Hill",
      "Faith Evans"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Which of the following rappers are from the West Coast?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Common",
      "Eminem",
      "None of the above",
      "Kanye west"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Which of the following rappers are from the East Coast?",
    answer: "Nas",
    options: [
      "50 Cent",
      "Dr. Dre",
      "Ludacris",
      "Nas"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "Which club has the highest number of trophies in spain?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Real Madrid",
      "Barcelona",
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Espanyol"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "Messi scored his first ever hat trick against which spanish club?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Real Betis",
      "Getafe",
      "Athletic Bilbao",
      "Real Madrid"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "2010 Fifa World Cup best player named Diego Forlan who played which spanish clubs?",
    answer: "Villareal and Atletico Madrid",
    options: [
      "Villareal and Atletico Madrid",
      "Villareal and Sevilla",
      "Real Madrid and Real Sociedad",
      "Atletico Madrid and Real Betis"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 31,
    question: "Which year did Messi scored his first ever hat trick against Real Madrid?",
    answer: "2007",
    options: [
      "2009",
      "2008",
      "2007",
      "2010"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 32,
    question: "Which is the oldest club in spain?",
    answer: "Sevilla",
    options: [
      "Real Madrid",
      "Sevilla",
      "Barcelona",
      "Athletic Club"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 33,
    question: "Who has won the most number of 'Zamora Trophy' by keeping highest amount of clean sheets in La Liga history?",
    answer: "Jan Oblak",
    options: [
      "Iker Casillas",
      "Victor Valdes",
      "Mark-Andre ter Stegen",
      "Jan Oblak"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 34,
    question: "Which stadium in spain has the highest seating capacity with 99,354 seats?",
    answer: "Camp Nou",
    options: [
      "Estadio Vicente Calderon",
      "Estadio Santiago Bernabeu",
      "Camp Nou",
      "RCDE Stadium"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 35,
    question: "Who was the first Real Madrid's manager?",
    answer: "Arthur Johnson",
    options: [
      "Juande Ramos",
      "Vicente del Bosque",
      "Fabio Capello",
      "Arthur Johnson"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 36,
    question: "AC Milan was founded in December 1899. Which English city were the club's founders from?",
    answer: "Nottingham",
    options: [
      "Nottingham",
      "Birmingham",
      "Bergamo",
      "Venice"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 37,
    question: "Which club, famous for their purple shirts, were the first-ever winners of the European Cup Winners' Cup in 1961?",
    answer: "Fiorentina",
    options: [
      "Juventus",
      "Fiorentina",
      "Roma",
      "Napoli"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "In which year did AC Milan win their first Campionato?",
    answer: "1901",
    options: [
      "1901", 
      "1900",
      "1902",
      "1905"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 39,
    question: "Who was AC Milan's captain in the 2003-04 season?",
    answer: "Paolo Maldini",
    options: [
      "Roberto Antonelli", 
      "Frank Baresi",
      "Caesar Maldini",
      "Paolo Maldini"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 40,
    question: "Which striker was topscorer three times in the 90s, when he played for Lazio?",
    answer: "Giuseppe Signori",
    options: [
      "Gabriel Batistuta", 
      "Giuseppe Signori",
      "Roberto Baggio",
      "Ciro Immobile"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 41,
    question: "Against which Spanish side did Juventus win the UEFA Cup in 1977?",
    answer: "Athletico Bilbao",
    options: [
      "Osasuna", 
      "Sevilla",
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Athletico Bilbao"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 42,
    question: "The first FIFA World Cup tournament was held in",
    answer: "1930",
    options: [
      "1930", 
      "1929",
      "1940",
      "1928"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 43,
    question: "Which country became the first from Africa to compete at a World Cup finals?",
    answer: "Egypt",
    options: [
      "Egypt", 
      "Morocco",
      "Tunisia",
      "Algeria"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 44,
    question: "Which country was the first to win two World Cups?",
    answer: "Italy",
    options: [
      "Brazil", 
      "Scotland",
      "Italy",
      "Germany"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 45,
    question: "No country outside of Europe or South America has ever won the men’s World Cup. True or False?",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "Neither", 
      "Both",
      "False",
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 46,
    question: "What was bizarre about Australia’s qualification for the 1998 World Cup?",
    answer: "They were unbeaten but still didn’t qualify for the tournament",
    options: [
      "They competed with the CONMEBOL nations for a place", 
      "They had four different managers",
      "They were unbeaten but still didn’t qualify for the tournament",
      "None of their starting XI against Fiji was born in Australia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 47,
    question: "Who won the top scorer title at the tournament on Mexican soil in 1986?",
    answer: "Gary Lineker",
    options: [
      "Diego Maradona", 
      "Gary Lineker",
      "Michel Platini",
      "Zico"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 48,
    question: "This is the first tournament for both Lionel Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo. How many goals did they score each (2006)?",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "4", 
      "6",
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 49,
    question: "Who won the Best Young Player award in 2014?",
    answer: "Paul Pogba",
    options: [
      "Memphis Depay", 
      "James Rodriguez",
      "Paul Pogba",
      "Luke Shaw"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 50,
    question: "The 2018 tournament is a record-setting tournament for the number of-",
    answer: "Most own goals",
    options: [
      "Most own goals", 
      "Most goals",
      "Most hat-tricks",
      "Most red cards"
    ]
  },
    
];

